usually after talking this long there
are some of you wondering if I'm gay or
not I knew it I'm not gay
I don't know what sexual orientation I
am what's the one where you like girls
but none of them like you back
it's called lonely that's what it's
called I'll tell you what not a lot of
people are supportive of lonely people
or like look you can be lonely in
private just don't be flamboyantly
lonely in public bumming us out man if
you're gay you get to come out of the
closet but if you're lonely you stay in
the closet you come out of your parents
basement you come out as gay it's
celebrated to people go wow you're so
brave for accepting yourself but if you
come out as lonely it's just sad you're
like I don't know how to tell you this
but I'm very lonely right now and they
don't say you're brave either they say
why are you talking to me I don't know
you I came out as lonely to my parents
though they're very supportive they're
like well Alex we can't say we weren't
suspicious
ever since your little kid we could tell
that no one liked you but we love you
very much gay marriage is legal now but
we still live in a society where lonely
people can't get married it's not right
I'm going to take it to the Supreme
Court even then I think the judges would
be like yeah we can't find anyone for
you we've all conferred and it's the
majority opinion of this judicial body
that you're kind of icky actually it's
the legal term problem is I can't raise
awareness for my cause I can't raise
awareness for loneliness
I can't have a lonely Pride Parade first
off I'm not proud about it at all if I
did have a parade who would come
this would be me alone on the street
waving at nobody
lonely people are discriminated against
you can't get married you also you can't
do we can't ride in the carpool lane
carpooling is discrimination against
lonely people it's the Jim Crow of the
highway
carpooling has its own symbol too there
is a symbol to my oppression my friends
that is the diamond symbol it's like the
swastika for lonely people it's rude
they picked the diamond to remind us of
the diamond on the wedding ring we'll
never have to buy dating is hard and I
was a young man they told me that in
order to be a gentleman you had to have
chivalry recently I looked up what the
word chivalry means and this is true it
comes from a medieval French word that
means horsemanship and I read that and
like you're telling me being a gentleman
is based on how medieval people treated
horses and we're not even talking about
polite medieval people we're talking
about French medieval people that also
means they came up with the horse
etiquette before they came up with the
women etiquette by the time they got to
how to treat women they're just like
let's just carry off as a horse rules
and we've been using the horse rules to
this day women come back from dates
essentially going he didn't make me feel
equestrian at all her friends like you
deserve to be treated like a horse Cindy
you're a lady
you've got the ponytail and everything
how much more clear can it be I want to
treat women with respect but if it's
based on horsemanship that seems
degrading like do you know why it's
polite to open doors for women it's
because horses cannot do it
women are totally capable of opening
their own doors nowadays they say it's
impolite to text a girl to ask her out
but according to these rules the most
polite thing to do this coach let's go
trusty steeds oh and you never want to
talk to a girl from the side either you
might spook her
whoa easy girl easy we're just going to
the Olive Garden I'll get you a sugar
cube just calm down now you should click
click on something anything I'm being
held here against my will please click
something so they'll let me go please
click please